welcome to new every day it is
毎日新しいことを歓迎します
Thanksgiving now if you're watching from
あなたが から 見ているなら今感謝祭
anywhere but America you're going what
アメリカ以外のどこでも
no it's American Thanksgiving and so we
いいえ、それはアメリカの感謝祭だと私たちは
are doing a special Thanksgiving episode
特別な感謝祭のエピソードを やっ ています
because what is there more to be
より多くのことがあるから
thankful for then Sunday football well
当時の日曜日のサッカーに感謝
that's what we're talking about today
それが 私たちが今日話していることです
we're gonna tell you a little bit about
我々はつもりあなた について 少し 教えています
Thanksgiving dinner we did here and
私たちがここでやった感謝祭のディナー
Canada for some students in our area and
私たちの 地域 で一部の学生のためのカナダ、
we're just gonna talk about being
私たちはただ話をするつもりです
thankful and what that means and what do
感謝し、それが何を意味し 、何をするのか
we have to be thankful for so don't go
感謝 しなければならないので行かないで
anywhere
どこでも
stick around this is you every day with
あなた と毎日 あるこの周りの固執
Jeff Weston Scribus
ジェフウェストンスクリブス
[Music]
[音楽]
welcome to new everyday so glad you're
あなたがしているので、喜んで 新しい 日常 へようこそ
here I'm Jeff Weston and I'm Lawrence
私はJeff Westonです、そして Lawrence です。
Cruz and it's Thanksgiving I know we
Cruzさん、ありがとうございます
mentioned that already it's an exciting
すでに 興奮 し て いると述べた
time I love Thanksgiving because I love
私は大好き だから 感謝祭を愛する時間
the food like as you can tell I I do
あなたがIIを言うことができるように食べ物は
enjoy my food yeah I thought about
自分の食べ物を楽しむ
soccer game but I'm like no I'm sitting
サッカーの試合だけど私は座っていないみたいだ
on this couch it's not gonna happen well
この ソファの 上に それが つもり も 起きていません
no yeah we're talking Thanksgiving today
今日は感謝祭を話している
and you know if you're watching in
で見ているかどうか
Canada you only do Thanksgiving a couple
カナダあなただけ の感謝祭に カップルを 行います
of weeks ago get these guys a calendar
数週間前これらの人たちにカレンダーを手に入れよう
well no we are celebrating Thanksgiving
私たちは 感謝祭 を祝っています
from American Thanksgiving that is this
このある アメリカの感謝祭から
weekend and so we wanted to kind of talk
週末なので話をしたかった
about Thanksgiving and it's kind of we
感謝祭について、それは私たちのようなものです
tied in both between the Canadian
カナダの間で両方で結ばれる
Thanksgiving the American Thanksgiving
アメリカの感謝祭
because at our church we did a
私たちの教会 では
Thanksgiving dinner for some college
いくつかの 大学への感謝祭のディナー
students and so you're gonna see in just
学生たち、そしてあなたはただで見るつもりです
a few minutes what some of the students
数分で何人かの生徒たち
are thankful for and so that's a tie-in
感謝しているので、それは 提携です
to the Canadian Thanksgiving and then
カナダの感謝祭へ
we're gonna flip over and we're gonna
私たちはひっくり返るつもりだそして私たちはつもりだ
talk today on American Thanksgiving so
そのアメリカの感謝祭 で 、今日の話
there you go over time the two countries
そこにあなたは時間をかけて二国間行きます
together and if you're not in Canada or
一緒にカナダにいないのなら
the US and you're watching and it's not
アメリカとあなたが見ているのではない
your Thanksgiving well then you could
それでは、感謝祭を
just join along for the ride now you're
ちょうど あなたがしている今、 乗るために沿って参加
the one who had kind of spearheaded the
ある種の先導者は
Thanksgiving that we had at the church
教会 でいただいた感謝祭
well I was privileged to play a big role
私は大きな役割を果たす特権を与えられました
in it for sure
確かにその中に
actually the back story on that Jeff is
実際にそのジェフの裏話は
for some time I've wanted to do
しばらくの間私がやりたかっ た
something to just be kind to the sea of
海に優しくなるための何か
students that's just two kilometers down
たった 2キロ 下 の学生
the road sea is a very appropriate word
道路の海 はとても適切な言葉です
there yeah yeah all kinds of them and
そうそうすべての種類の
one day a young lady came up to me and
ある日、若い女性が 私の ところにやってき た。
said you know what I think it'd be a
あなたは私がそれがなると思うものを知っていると言いました
good idea for us to reach out and that's
私たちが手を差し伸べるのは良い考えだし、それはそれです
all I need it it's like okay you know
必要なのはそれだけでいい
what this is God moving in more than
これは神が何よりも動いているということです。
just one heart and so really from that
ただ一つの心、そしてそれから本当に
conversation we just decided we're gonna
会話 我々はちょうど 決心する つもり だ と 決めました
do this and so so many people in our
私たちの 多くの 人々
church right rallied they we they went
教会は彼らが行った彼らを正しく集めた
out and bought the turkeys they cook the
七面鳥を買いに
turkeys they were asking do you want
彼らが求めていた七面鳥
stuffing you want gravy it's like
肉汁が欲しい
potatoes carrots and I mean it was the
ジャガイモニンジンと私はそれがあったわけ
meal of the century it was a very nice
世紀の食事は とても素敵でした
meal I was hungry
おなかがすいた食事
I'm out front man in the camera and
私はカメラでフロントマンアウトだと
getting you know students you know
知っている学生を知ってもらう
perspective on what they're thankful for
彼らが何に感謝しているかについての展望
and I'm watching all this food go by and
そして私は この食べ物が全部 通り過ぎるのを 見 て います
I'm like oh that's good I mean it was
ああいいね
awesome I mean it was the the full meal
素晴らしい私はそれが完全な食事だったことを意味
done excellently home cook but I mean
家庭料理はとてもよくできていますが
everybody went all in and even the
誰も が オールインし、 さらには
ambience well it wasn't just like you
雰囲気 だけでなく 、それはちょうど あなたのよう ではなかったです
know church basement ack-ack we like
教会の地下室を知っている
yeah there was the white shirt the black
そう白いシャツは黒い
pants like everybody was looking fancy
みんな ファンシー に見えたパンツ
definitely not a hunting camping and I
間違いなく狩猟キャンプではない
know I hear the food is really good on
私は食べ物が本当に良いのを聞くのを知っている
the hunting camp yes they are you know
狩猟キャンプはい、彼らはあなたが知っていますか
that's a hunting camp but you're right
それは狩猟キャンプ ですが、その通りです
it was like it was like a five-star
それは 五つ星のようだった
experience people dressed in black
黒に身を包んだ人々の体験
bottoms white tops
ボトムスホワイトトップス
young people ready to serve like it's
若者はそれのように奉仕する準備ができて
like what and not ready they did boy
何が好きで準備ができていない彼らは男の子をやった
with excellence yeah
優秀でええ
and so that was great what a privilege
そしてそれはなんという特権だったか
Jeff I had to be able to actually sit
私が実際に座る ことができなければならなかったジェフ
down it's often I'm so honored and at
私はとても光栄に思っています
the church where I serve and the people
私が仕える教会と人々
allow a pastor will serve and you sit
牧師が奉仕することを許可し、あなたが 座る
down and so for young men who were brand
ブランドだった若い男性の ために
new to the college just down the street
通りのすぐ下の大学に新しい
a Community College and they had only
コミュニティカレッジと 彼らは
been in the country for one month right
右の 1 ヶ月 の国 に ありました
because there were international
国際的だったから
students yeah that's right actually all
学生ええそれは右 、実際にすべて です
of them happen to be from India and to
それらをインドから と の ことが起こります
the guys were wearing turbans and which
みんながターバン を 着 ていて
I found interesting too I mean I've seen
私も見たことがある という意味私 も面白い
that all of my life that's not nothing
私の 人生の すべては それだけではないということ
new at all but to sit down openly and
オープンに座ること 以外はまったく新しい
and they were asking me all kinds of
彼らは私にいろいろな種類の
questions hey tell us about your country
あなたの国について 教え てください
tell us about Barry tell us about what
バリーについて教えてください
this thing called Halloween they had
ハロウィンと呼ばれる この 事は彼らが持っていた
heard about that was kind of yeah you
それについて聞いたことがある
know tell it I thought that's good I
それを教えて知っている
said hey we're anyway they were so I
とにかく私たちはとにかく
said how are you loving the meal I mean
あなたはどうやって食事を愛していますか
they're they're they're young man it's
彼らは彼らです 彼らは彼らは若い男ですそれは
like this is awesome can we have some
これはすごいですね。
more and and the people come in is
もっとそしてそして人々がやってくる
serving them more it was just excellent
もっと彼らに仕えることそれはただ優秀だった
I said tell me about your turban is that
私は あなたのターバンについて 教え て
okay and they proceeded to tell me all
大丈夫 、 彼らは私に すべて を伝え始めた
about that you know and I and I had I
あなたが 知っ ていることについて 私と私は 私 に持っていた
had heard that some people don't cut
何人かの人々はカットしないと 聞い た
their hair and that they kept on doing
彼らの髪と彼らは やっ て続けた こと
that and
あれと
and apparently that's true but not
どうやら それは本当ではなく、
everybody does that okay and that times
みなさんは大丈夫と その倍ということありません
are a-changing where two guys didn't
2人の男が変わらなかったところは変わります
have turbans but two did and yet they
ターバンがありますが、2つはありましたが、それでも彼らは
had the same belief system and so there
同じ信念体系を持っていたので、そこに
was just this level of change I mean it
ちょうどこのレベルの変化でし た
was just I love people I love being with
私 は 一緒 にいる こと を愛する人々を愛し ている だけだった
people and to hear their story and them
人々 と彼らの物語と彼らを聞くこと
to ask me about ours and to be able to
私たちのことについて私に尋ねることができるように
serve them and say hey I know you might
彼らに仕え、あなたがそうするかもしれないことを私は知っている
be missing home but welcome to our
ホーム欠落しているが、 私たち を歓迎 します
country and they loved it and I think I
国と彼らはそれを愛し、私は 私 だと思います
loved it even more I know that they like
私は彼らが好きであることを私は知っています
the chocolate cake I think I don't think
チョコレートケーキ私は 考えていない と思います
there's a single student that less than
一人の生徒 より少ない
four rounds of dessert on the chocolate
チョコレート のデザート4ラウンド
cake well I'll tell you what well we had
ケーキよく私 たちが持っていた ものを教えてあげる
plenty of it but one thing we've learned
たくさんありますが、 私たちが学んだことの 1つ
is that the international students at
留学生は
least that come our way they're not they
少なくともそれは私たちの やり方 で来る 彼らは彼らではない
don't fancy pumpkin pie ya know and who
カボチャのパイを空想しないでくださいそして誰が 知っ ている
knew I mean you would think Thanksgiving
感謝祭だと思うだろう
do the same thing and it's like we have
同じことをして、それ は私たちが持っているような ものです
learned enough where all that pumpkin
そのすべてのカボチャが十分に学んだところ
pie is just sitting there we could have
パイはただそこに座っているだけです
been smart just about pumpkin yeah we
ちょうど ええ、私たちが カボチャ についてスマートき
could we could have just had our fill
塗りつぶし ができただけ
for the rest of the year
年 の 残り のために
next time I'll be thinking about no we
次回は、私はノーたちを考えることになります
bought apple crumble and I mean hey who
りんごのクランブルを買ったと 私はちょっと誰を意味
doesn't like chocolate I mean if you
もしあれば私が意味するチョコレートが好きではありません。
don't we can pray for you right now
今すぐ あなたのために祈ることはできませんか
that's no troll yeah okay here we're
それはトロールで はありません
here I'm just going wild on the food now
ここで私は 今食べ物に 夢中 になります
it was a great experience and we had we
それは素晴らしい経験でしたし、
had a full class fall I guess you'd I'd
フルクラスでの転倒がありました
say of students that came and almost all
来た学生のことを 言う
of them brand new to the country yeah
それらのええ 国に新 ブランド
and some of them had never stepped foot
そして彼らの何人かは足を踏み入れたことがない
in a church before so that was kind of
以前の教会では そうだった
neat right to have them kind of step in
それらを一種 の ステップインに するためのきちんとした権利
and be like oh so this is what a church
ああそうだから、 これが教会だ
looks like okay it's not as scary and
それが怖い ようではありません大丈夫のように見え、
even some of them have I think I've seen
それらのいくつかでさえ私は私が見たと思う
them back on on a Sunday service I think
それらは、背面の日曜礼拝 に 私は 思います
that's the truth and it's amazing what
それは真実であり、 それは素晴らしいものです
love will do you know it's just a love
愛はあなたがそれがただの愛であることを知っていますか
opens the door just to keep on being
ちょうど で あること に保つためにドアを開けます
loving and just sharing life and if we
愛情と人生を共有しているだけで
we are people who are here who are
私たちはここにいる人々です
thankful there who are thankful and and
感謝して いる人、そして
love the Lord just being who we are and
ちょうど我々が誰であるかという、 主を 愛し
welcome oh man how cool it yeah it's
ああ、なんてクールだよ
rewarding to see that other people would
であろうと、他の人を 見 てやりがい
respond to that love and keep on coming
その愛に応えて来て続けて
by
によって
right and maybe even another meal or two
正しいそして多分別の食事か2つ
here or there examine out with some of
ここまたはそこの一部で 出調べます
them
それら
let's head and it's been great yeah it's
頭を上げよう、それは素晴らしいね
been very good so yeah so while they
とても良かった のでそうそう
were eating away I was in the hallway
離れて 食べていた 私は、 廊下に いました
had the camera set up and just you know
カメラを設定 し、 ちょうどあなたが知っ ていました
as they're coming in and coming and
彼らが入って来て来ているように
leaving at the end of the day I'm saying
私が言っている一日 の 終わりに出発
hey are you willing to just tell us for
ちょっと私達に言っても構わないと思っています
a second what it is that you're thankful
それはあなたが感謝しているということです
for because we want to get a perspective
私たちは 遠近感 を得たいからです
and for some of them they were
そして彼らのうちの何人かは彼らは
international students some were from
留学生の中には、
Bari I think another one was from a
バリ私はもう一つが から だったと思う
couple hours away so you know God
あなたが神を知っているように数時間離れて
brought perspectives different ages
異なる年齢の視点をもたらした
stuff like that so yeah let's take a
そのようなものは、 そうそうさんは見てみましょう
look and see what our students are
私たちの学生が何であるかを見て見てください
thankful for hi I'm Alex I'm thankful
こんにちは私はアレックス私は感謝しています
for friends and family they really made
彼らが本当に作った友達や家族のために
this possible to have a nice dinner and
素敵な夕食を持っているこれは可能と
the opportunity to be here in Canada so
カナダにここにいる機会
thank you all and Happy Thanksgiving
あなたのすべてのハッピー感謝祭に感謝
hi this is a promising from India and
こんにちはこれは インドから の 有望です
actually I came to Canada this year and
実際に私は今年、カナダに来 て、
it's been a month only and I've been
それは一ヶ月だけされていると私はしてきた
here and I am thankful for everything
ここと私はすべてに感謝 しています
like my parents has done a lot for me
私の両親 が 私のために たくさん やってくれたように
and they have sent me to such a
そして彼らは 私 をこんなところに 送っ た
beautiful country and talking about the
美しい国と の話
day yesterday it was absolutely amazing
昨日は本当にすごかった
to meet such such amazing people and to
こんな素晴らしい人たちに会い、
have such a nice dinner and like
こんな素敵な夕食を食べたい
absolutely delighted and I'm so happy to
本当にうれしいです
be here
ここ に
my name is Danielle and this
私の名前はダニエルとこれ
Thanksgiving I'm grateful for all my
感謝祭私は私のすべてに感謝しています
friends here at Calvary Church who have
ここ カルバリー教会の 友人たち
let me come into the youth meeting on
の青少年会議に参加させてください
Sundays and I'm grateful that you know
日曜日と私はあなたが知っていることに感謝しています
we're all so loved by God and they of
我々はすべての ように の 神と 彼ら に 愛されています
the capacity to show that love to
その愛を示す能力
everyone who they need so thank you guys
彼らが必要としてくれた皆さん、本当にありがとう
for being so great
とても素晴らしい ことのために
hi my name is Bhavik I'm from India and
こんにちは私の名前はBhavik です私はインドから来ました
I just came to Canada to complete my
私はカナダにやって来たばかりです。
studies and it's just I've just wanted
勉強し 、それはちょうど私が ほしかっ ただけです
thanks to my parents and my family
両親 と私の家族に感謝します
members to send me over here for new
ここに 私を送ってくれる メンバー
opportunities and I also want to thank
機会と私も 感謝し たい
and thank you and I thank to this team
そして 私 はこのチーム に感謝 し ます
who invited us here for this
誰が私たちをここに招待してくれたの
Thanksgiving dinner it was really a
感謝祭のディナー は本当に
great time with you guys and special
あなたと素晴らしい時間を過ごして
thanks to Lawrence who addressed us so
私達にそう言ったローレンスのおかげで
well and guided us through this culture
この文化を通して私たちを導きました
thank you for everything we had a great
私たちが素晴らしかったすべてに感謝します
experience and I am so thankful for our
経験と私は私たちのためにとても感謝しています
church community I think I was really
教会のコミュニティ私は本当にいたと思います
excited about tonight coming for the
今夜のために来ることに興奮して
dinner and it was so it thrills me every
夕食と、 それはそれが すべて私をワクワクさせるよう でし た
time when I see so many people
私は非常に多くの人々を参照してください時間
I'm just so freely giving of their time
私は彼らの時間をとても自由に与えている
and their food yes we should enjoy that
そして彼らの食べ物 はい、私たち は それ を楽しむべき です
food it's it's I love our church family
食べ物 それは私の教会の家族を愛することです
we are all they're just amazing that's
私たちは皆 、彼らは ただ素晴らしい です
great I'm Alexia and I am very thankful
私はAlexiaです、そして私はとても感謝しています
for Jesus so thankful for again our
再び私たちのために 、イエスのためにとても感謝
church community be coming from like far
教会共同体は遠くから来ている
away and just getting welcomed right
すぐに歓迎される
away in and feeling like family and I'm
家族のように感じている
thankful for stuffing now that I know
私が知っている今詰め物に感謝
it's not guts
ガッツじゃない
[Laughter]
[笑い]
everything stick around for more from
からすべてのものの周りに固執する
new every day for a limited time get
限られた時間のための新しい毎日 を取得
your hands on limited-edition shirts
限定版のシャツを手にする
from the category 5 TV network these
カテゴリー5のTVネットワークから
high quality shirts are manufactured by
高品質のシャツはによって製造されています
teespring a fundraising website and your
募金のウェブサイトとあなたを teespring
purchase will help support the shows we
購入は私たちがショーをサポートするのに役立ちます
produce get yours today and send us your
農産物は今日あなたのものを入手して私たちにあなたのものを送ります
pictures to be featured on the
上で紹介する写真
corresponding show visit cap 5 dot TV
対応するショー訪問キャップ5ドットテレビ
slash shirts to support us and get your
私達を支え、あなたのものを手に入れるためにシャツを切る
official Network shirt today count 5 dot
公式ネットワークシャツは本日 5ドットカウント
TV slash shirts welcome back we are
テレビスラッシュシャツ歓迎私たち は
talking Thanksgiving it is American
それはアメリカ人です感謝祭
Thanksgiving this weekend and so if
今週末、そして もしそうなら感謝祭
you're watching from the USA
アメリカから 見 ている
happy Thanksgiving TV Thanksgiving
Happy Thanksgiving TV 感謝祭
you're watching from somewhere else in
他の場所 から見 ている
the world that's not celebrating
祝っていない 世界
Thanksgiving happy Thanksgiving to you
幸せな感謝祭あなたに感謝祭
exactly so you know I've I've had the
まさにあなたは私が私を持ってい た ことを知って いる
privilege of being in the States now for
今アメリカ にいるという特権
Thanksgiving twice and I will move there
2回感謝祭をします
no no I for some reason feel tied to the
私は何らかの理由で私はに縛られていると感じる
snow here in Canada I suppose there some
ここカナダでは雪が私は そこに いくつかの 仮定します
state might have fun to do with the back
状態は背中 と関係があるかもしれません
your wife live here yeah but you know it
あなたの妻はここに住んでいますがあなたはそれを知っています
was it was West Virginia where I was
私がいたのはウェストバージニアだったのか
visiting with some friends there in a
で友達 と一緒に訪問
beautiful beautiful area but one of the
美しいエリア
things I loved is that when it comes to
私が愛したことはそれがなるとなるということです
Thanksgiving down there and maybe this
ありがとう ございます
isn't the case with every family but the
すべての家族に当てはまる わけではありません が、
family came from everywhere you know
家族は あなたが知っているどこからでも 来た
like for us it's like oh we're three
私たちのようにそれはああ私たちのように 3つ のような
hours away it's you know we're not gonna
数時間後には、私たちは行きたくない
make it you know for this celebration
このお祝いのためにあなたが知っているようにする
down there it's like oh yeah we're from
そこにそれは 我々がからだそうそうようなもの です
Oklahoma but we're just gonna drive over
オクラホマ州しかし私達は追い越すつもり だ
here to Pennsylvania we're gonna go you
ここペンシルバニアへ 私達はあなたに行くつもりです
know it's like they're all coming in
みんなが入ってき ているようだ
spending hours and hours and hours on
時間と時間 と 時間
the road and it was really neat to see
道路とそれ は 見て 本当に きれい でした
the family perspective as a Thanksgiving
感謝祭としての家族の見方
down there and you know the whole
あそこにあなたは全体を知っています
culture of watching the football and
サッカー観戦の文化
they were all around the team
彼らはすべてチームの周りにいました
and you know given the potshots to each
そして、あなたはそれぞれにpotshotsを与えられて知っています
other and I just see what your guide
他と私は ちょうどあなたのガイドを参照してください
Danny I dropped the ball that's all my
ダニー私はボールを落とした
team's getaway it was it was a lot of
チームの 逃走それは たくさんだった
fun but I really enjoyed it but was so
楽しかったけど本当に楽しかったけど
neat is just truly how thankful they are
きちんとしているということは、本当に本当に感謝して いる ということ です。
yeah and I find sometimes here in Canada
ええと私は時々ここカナダで見つけます
I've noticed that some some families
いくつかの家族がいることに気づきました
it's just about getting together and
それだけで一緒になってのことだと
that's it but when I was down with my
それはそれですが、私は 私 と一緒 にいたとき
friends in West Virginia for them it was
ウェストバージニア州の友人たちには
they stopped and they said okay every
彼らは立ち止まり、 彼らは毎回大丈夫と言った
one of you what is it that you're
それは あなたがしている ということです何の1
thankful for and it was so neat to go
感謝し 、それは 行くの はとてもきれい だった
around this table of 25 people and hear
25人のこのテーブルの周りに聞いて
what at what every person is thankful
どんな人に感謝しているのか
for different perspectives and you know
異なる視点のために、 あなたが知っています
from those who are Christians those who
クリスチャンである人々から
are not and it was really really neat to
そうではありません、それは本当に本当にきれいでした
hear kind of that heartfelt thought of
その心からの考えのようなものを聞く
yet you know this is what I've gone
まだあなたはこれが私が行ったのだということを知っている
through this year and this is what I'm
今年を通じて、これ は私がしているものです
thankful for you know and and and God's
あなたが 知っていることに感謝し、 そしてそしてそして神のもの
taking care of me this way really yeah
この よう にして私の 世話をすること は 本当にうん
and it was really really cool I truly
本当にすごくかっこいい です
enjoyed it was one of the highlights of
それはのハイライトの一つだった楽しかった
being in the States for me as though I
私のためにアメリカ にいる かのようにI
Thanksgiving that is it that's a cool
それはそれ がクール だ感謝祭 です
experience I mean hey we're not under no
経験私たちは決して下にいないということです
illusions here I guarantee you that's
幻想はここにあり ます
not happening at every table well
すべてのテーブルでうまくいっている わけではありません
exactly yeah boy that's that's a great
それは素晴らしいです
experience to be part of yeah I really
ええの一部 になるための経験私は本当に
was what did it stir something in you
それはあなたの中で何かをかき混ぜたのですか
Jeff you think you're ah I think I don't
Jeff あなた はあなたがああだと思う 私はしない と思う
know if it really stirred anything but
それは本当に何かをかき混ぜるかどうかを知っている
it was really it was just kind of nice
本当に よかったです
yeah
ええ
to just to see genuine thankfulness yeah
本物の感謝を見るためだけに
especially in today's culture where it's
特に 今日の文化 で は
hustle and bustle and it's about you
喧騒とそれはあなたのことです
know how can I stab you in the back to
どのように私はあなたを後ろに突き刺すことができるか知っている
get ahead in life at least you know in
少なくともあなたが知っている人生を先に進む
major cities that's kind of how it can
それができる方法の一種の主要都市
feel yeah but it was it was neat to just
ええ感じますが、それだけできれいだった
have everybody stop and go it doesn't
みんな立ち止まって 行かないで
matter what's happening this is what I'm
何が起こっていてもこれは私がしていることです
thankful for and they focused on the
に感謝し、彼らはに焦点を当て た
positive yeah and you know the the
そうだね、あなたは知って いる
patriarch of the family she was you know
彼女はあなたが知っていた家族の家長
the mother she's down there and she's
彼女はそこにいます、そして彼女は
like you know born and raised in the
あなたが生まれ育ったことを知っているように
church and everything was about God and
教会とすべてが 神 についての ものであり、
so thankful and even the tough times in
とても感謝 しているし、厳しい時代でさえ
life she she sat there and said you know
彼女は彼女がそこに座って、あなたが知っていると言った人生
but I'm thankful for God carrying me
しかし、私 を運んでいる神に 感謝 します
through and like there was no negativity
ネガティブさがなかったように
to the bad situations in life you know
あなたが知っ ている 人生 の悪い状況に
and they had lost a family member and
そして彼らは 家族を 失った。
she's like you know they weren't saved
彼女はあなたが彼らが救われなかったことを知っているようです
but I'm so thankful that for the time
しかし、私はその間とても感謝し ています
that I had even just to talk to them
私は 彼ら と話 をする だけでも
about Christ and the
キリストについて
influence that they've had in my life
彼らが私の人生にもたらした影響
and this is the way that you know gods
これは 、あなたが神を知っている方法 です
directed their like everything was about
すべて が約だっ たように彼らに指示した
you know how God had was in everything
あなたは神が すべてのことに あったことを知ってい ます
within her life and it was really neat
彼女の人生 の中 、それは 本当にきれいでした
to see that was a choice
それが選択だったのを見ること
it really was yeah to give emphasis to
重点を置くの は本当にうれしかった
those things that they're thankful for
彼らが 感謝 し ている こと
yeah it was it was really really just
ええそれは本当に本当にちょうどだったということでした
inspiring actually that's very cool I'm
感動は実際 には、 私は 非常にクールです
inspired as I hear you you share about
私はあなたがについて共有していると聞いているように感動
like I I mean I wasn't there but right
IIのように私は そこにい なかっ たが正しい
my imagine it take so my imagination
想像して みると想像できる
takes over I can picture this individual
引き継ぐ私はこの個人を描くことができます
and giving thanks and while you're
そして感謝しながら
speaking to me a favorite verse of mine
私 のお気に入りの詩 を私に話して
comes to my mind and I happen to have it
頭に浮かんできた
posted in our home but it's Philippians
私たちの家に掲示されますが、それはフィリピン人です
chapter 4 and verse 8 and it says
4章8節
whatever is true whatever is noble
貴であるものは何でも真実である ものは何でも
whatever is right whatever is pure
正しいものは何でも純粋なものは何でも
whatever is love lovely whatever is
素敵な愛は何されているものです
admirable if anything is excellent or
何か優れたものであれば賞賛に値する
praiseworthy think about such things
そのようなことについて賞賛に値する
Philippians chapter 4 verse 8 oh man
ピリピ人への 手紙第4章8節
that's exactly what she was and well
それはまさに彼女が いたものです
that's I'm listening to you thinking
それは私があなたの考えを聞いている
this is what this guy was doing yeah and
これはこの 男が そう やっていた もの です そして
make no mistake about it Jeff I I put
それを間違えないでJeff IIが置く
that verse on my wall in a place where I
私のいる場所で私の壁に
would see it regularly and I did that on
それを定期的に見るだろう そして私はそれをした
purpose because I I I know I live the
目的 IIIは、私が住んでいる知っている ので、
reality of not thinking about everything
すべてを考えないという 現実
good yes and it just weighs me down and
はい、それはちょうど私の体重を量ると
I thought Lord you're telling me
私はあなたが私に言っていると思った
something good I want to remind myself
私は自分自身を思い出させたい 良い何か
of the truth of your word that
あなたの 言葉の真実は
encourages me to think about good things
良い こと について考えることを私に勧めます
lovely excellent praise where the
素敵な優れた賞賛どこ
admirable true noble like there's a
あるような立派な真の 貴族
there's something good that happens
起こる何か良いことがあります
inside of me and even without you know
私の中でもあなたが知らなくても
around me as well when I start to think
私 が 考え 始めた とき も私の周りに
about things that are good yeah yeah you
あなたはええええ優れている ことについて
find that - yeah definitely yeah so God
それを見つける- ええ間違いなく そうそう神
said that for a reason and so it's just
理由とそれが ちょうど だと言いました
this is a good show to be part of like
これはのようであることの良いショーです
I'm yeah I'm thankful for yes I'm
ええ、ありがとうございます
thankful even right now it's good I'm
今でもありがたいです
feeling the love man
恋人を感じる
good you know it's funny you're talking
あなたが話しているのは面白いですよね
about your you know the scripture you've
あなたのことを知ってい ます
got up on the wall and and one that my
壁に起きて、そしてそれが私のこと
wife and I have up on the wall at home
妻と私は家の壁に立ち上がっています
it's kind of become like our life verse
それは 私たちの人生の詩 の ようになるようなものです
and I think I've mentioned it on a show
私は 番組で それ を 述べたと 思います
in the past but it's it's Jeremiah 29:11
過去には、それはエレミヤです29:11
for I know the plans I have for you
私はあなたのために私が持っている計画を知っているので
declares the Lord plans to prosper you
主 が あなた を繁栄させる ことを 計画していると 宣言する
not to harm you plans to give you a hope
害を与えないためにあなたに希望を与える 計画
and a future and a lot of times that's
そして未来と多く の時代
where people stop but I love the next
人が止まるところ、私は次が大好き
verse then you will call on me and come
その後、あなたは私に電話してくるでしょう
and pray to me and I will listen to you
そして私に 祈って ください、そして私はあなたに耳を傾けます
you will seek me and find me when you
あなたは私を探し、あなたが私を見つけるときに
seek me with all your heart and what I
すべてのあなたの 心 と私は 私を求めて
love about that scripture is it totally
その 聖典に興味があるのは完全にそれです
fits in with Thanksgiving God has a plan
感謝祭にはまります神は計画を持っています
for all of us mhm and it's a good plan
私たち みんなの ためには、 ええと、それは良い計画です
and even sometimes when we go through
そして 時々私達が通過するとき
not-so-good things it's all part of that
それほど良くない ことはすべてその一部 です
plan oh man are we sure yeah okay so I
ああ男計画私たちは確かにそう大丈夫そうですか
would I agree I'm just like wow hey
私はほんとにすごい ね
Laurence just a second hear what the
ほんの一瞬でローレンスは何を聞いて
preacher said oh and I think you know so
説教者は ああ 言った そして 私 はあなたがそう知っていると思う
often you hear the question - why is it
よく聞かれるのですが、なぜでしょう。
that good thing or bad things happen to
良いことか悪い ことが起こる
good people it's like okay well I'm
いい人、 いいじゃないですか
pretty sure Jesus got pulverized and
きっとイエスは微粉砕され 、
crucified on a cross that's not a great
それは 素晴らしいで はありません十字架に十字架につけ
thing but the good that came out of that
事それから出てきた良いです
we now have eternity in heaven like even
私たちは今も天国のように永遠にいる
with those plans that God has for us to
神が私たちのために持っている計画によって
carry us through those dark moments in
の暗い瞬間を通して私たちを運んでください
our life mmm he's got it all figured out
私たちの人生うーん、彼はそれをすべて 考え出し た
Wow Jeff that's a good word man so
うわー、 ジェフそれはいい言葉だ
there's always something to be thankful
感謝するものが常にあります
for even if it's nothing less than the
たとえそれが何 よりも少なくないとしても
gift of salvation and eternity in heaven
天国での救いと永遠の贈り物
you know and as we're here talking about
あなたが知っているそして我々がここに話しているように
Thanksgiving I think it doesn't matter
感謝祭私は それが問題ではない と思います
what you're going through and it doesn't
何を 通過 つもりだ し、それはしていません
matter the good or the bad there is
善と悪がある
something to be thankful for mm-hmm and
MM-HMMの感謝するために何かして
that is the gift of salvation and the
それが救いの賜物であり、
fact that God's got it all under control
神がすべてを支配しているという事実
well here okay you brought up this verse
さてここで大丈夫あなたはこの詩を育てた
well I'm thinking of her who for the joy
私は喜びのために彼女を考えています
set before him Jesus Christ endured the
イエス・キリストが彼の前に置かれた
cross that hardship yes but he knew that
その困難を乗り越えるそうですが、彼はそれを知っていました
there was a bigger picture and he was
もっと大きな絵があり、彼は
going to be willing to participate in
参加しても構わないと思っ て いる
something that he didn't like as much
彼はそれほど好きではなかった何か
because there was a bigger picture of
より大きな絵があったから
had namely the salvation of Jeff of
すなわちジェフの救いは
Lawrence many of you watching perhaps
ローレンスみんな見てる
you don't know the Lord yet as your
あなたはあなたのようにまだ主を知らない
Savior Jesus died for you he did it
救い主イエスは 、彼が それをやった あなたのために死にました
willingly he endured a brutal cross
喜んで彼は残忍な十字架に耐えました
because he knew he had thanks in his own
彼は自分で感謝の気持ちを知っていたから
heart towards his father that there was
彼の父親の方への心
a plan much bigger than his own
自分の計画よりはるかに大きい計画
suffering and he chose willingly to
苦しみ、 彼は喜んで
participate in that in order that we
それに参加するために
would know salvation if you don't know
あなたが知ら なければ救いを知っているだろう
him yet why don't you reach out and just
彼はまだあなたが手を差し伸べるしていない理由だけで
say God thank you for what you did for
神は あなたが何をしたか を ありがとう 言います
me would you cleanse me of all my sins
私の罪をすべて清めてください。
that's all you need to do as long as
それは あなたがいる限り 、行う必要があるすべて です
it's from your heart I promise you if
それが あれば 、私は あなたを約束し 、あなたの心からです
you reach out to God he knows what
あなたは 神に 手を差し伸べる
you're thinking he knows your heart and
あなたは彼があなたの心を知っていると思っています
he'll come and cleanse you oh you talk
彼は来て、あなたを清潔にしますあああなたが話します
about Thanksgiving what a Thanksgiving
感謝祭について
weekend that would be when one knows
週末は知っている時でしょう
what it is to have all of their sins
それは罪のすべてを 持っているものです
forgiven them the weight of sin taken
罪の重さを彼らに許した
off of you because it was once put upon
それは一度つけられたのであなたから離れて
Jesus who willingly went there right
喜んでそこへ行ったイエス
even though he was agonizing with sweat
たとえ彼が汗で苦しんでいたとしても
drops of blood father if there's another
他に血の父親がいれば
way but there is your plan is what I
しかしあなたの計画は私のものです
willingly submit to because I'm thankful
感謝しているので喜んで提出する
that you have a plan that's gonna save
あなたが保存する予定の計画があること
everybody who will call upon the name of
の 名前を 呼ぶ人は誰でも
the Lord wow that's a perspective and
主はすごいそれは視点だと
praise the Lord that's what I hear you
主を賛美するそれが 私があなたの言うことです
talking about yeah and yeah when things
ええとええ ときに物事を話す
aren't the best there's so many other
他にもたくさんあるので最高じゃない
things that we can be thankful for and
感謝 する こと が できるもの
when we think about it it's enough to
考えてみると
change the atmosphere isn't it really
雰囲気を変える
really is yes it's all about that
本当にそうです、それだけです。
perspective and so as we celebrate this
私たちがこれを祝うように
Thanksgiving this American Thanksgiving
このアメリカの感謝祭
you know truly think about what it is
あなたはそれが何であるかについて本当に考えることを知っています
that God has done in your life whether
神 が あなたの 人生になさったのは、
you know him or not he's had an impact
あなたは彼を知っているかどうか彼が影響を及ぼしたかどうか
on your life yeah and there are things
あなたの人生には うんそして もの が ある
to be thankful for and yeah I mean if
以下のために 感謝する と、ええ、私はあれば意味 します
there was a takeaway that would be it is
それは ある だろう お持ち帰りがありました
that you know to be thankful for yeah
あなたがええに感謝 する ことを知っている こと
yeah there are there's always something
ええ、 いつも何かあります
to be thankful for yeah and those people
そうそうとその人々に感謝すること
did it right that you were with the
あなたが一緒にいたことを正しくしました
states they gathered together on purpose
意図的に 一緒に集まった
to recount of those things yes hear the
そういったことを再考するために
word of the Lord Psalm 100 verse 4
詩篇100詩4の言葉
actually I had to memorize this in 19
実際に私は 19年に これを暗記しなければなりませんでした
eighty six as a matter of fact talking
事実の 話 として86
yeah your enter his gates with
ええ、あなた は彼の門に入り ます
Thanksgiving and go into his courts with
感謝祭 と 彼の裁判所に入ると
praise give thanks to him and praise his
賞賛は 彼に 感謝 し、彼を賞賛 する
name
名
yeah okay which part of that don't you
ええ、その部分は あなた で はない
understand more I got it that's right
もっと理解している
be thankful give him praise and this is
感謝して彼に賛美 を与えなさいそして これは
how God invites us to come to him did
神はどうやって私たちを彼に来るように招きましたか
you hear that he invites us to come to
あなたは彼がに来るために私たちを誘うことを聞きます
him I love that he's not some deistic
彼は、私は、彼はいくつかのdeisticないことを愛します
far away god no he says hey how you
遠くに 神の彼はどうやってあなたにちょっと言う
doing what's going on come on in and
中に 来る何が起こっていることと、
when you do how about how about entering
どうやって 入るのですか
into my presence with thanks and praise
感謝と賞賛をもって私の前に
I said I can do that yeah easy to do oh
私はああ 、私はそう 簡単に行うために それを行うことができました
that's it's a good one there's one more
それはもう一つ良いことです
- Jeff the Lord this is Psalm 28 verse 7
- 主なる ジェフ これは詩篇第28編第 7 節
it says the Lord is my strength and
それは主が私の力であり、
shield I trust him with all my heart can
シールド 私 は心からできる 限り 彼を信頼して いる
you say that with the psalmist I can
あなたは詩人と私ができると言う
today yeah I trust them with all my
今日ええ私は すべてで それらを信頼します
heart he helps me and my heart is filled
彼は私を助け、 私の心は満たされている
with joy I burst out in songs of
喜び をもって私 は
Thanksgiving
感謝祭
Psalm 28 verse 7 boy that that's a good
詩篇第28編第 7 節 それはいいことだ
one too isn't it yeah and that's not
1 つもそうで はありません 、 そうではありません
just I mean it's clear you can hear the
あなたが聞くことができるのは明らかだ
psalmist heart in that one it's not just
その中の詩人の 心は それだけではありません
a one-day year Thanksgiving it's every
1日の年感謝祭
day yeah yeah amazing that an entire
その日 全体で 驚くべき こと
nation comes on purpose to celebrate the
国は祝うために意図的に来ます
theme of Thanksgiving boy I think it is
感謝祭の少年のテーマ私はそれだと思います
something that we could do every day of
毎日 できる こと
the year yeah for sure yeah absolutely
確か に年ええええ 絶対に
well we're out of time and football is
まあ 我々は時間がないし 、サッカーは
gonna be coming on a little bit so
少し来てそうする つもり です
Patriots oh did I say that okay that's
愛国者 ああ 私は 大丈夫だ と言ったの ですか
all the time we got for you enjoy your
私達があなたのために得た すべての時間 はあなたのを楽しむ
food get absolutely stuffed and enjoy
食べ物は絶対に詰め込まれて楽しむ
the football or whatever it is that you
フットボール、 それが あなたなら 何でも
decide to do is to celebrate today and
行うことを 決定することは 、今日祝うことで 、
have a wonderful week we'll see you next
素敵な一週間を過ごしましょう
week gobble gobble
ぐらつきぐらつき
catch a new episode of you every day
毎日 あなたの新しいエピソードをキャッチ
every Friday morning at new everyday TV
毎週金曜日の朝、新しい毎日の テレビで
we're also on roku cody flex youtube
私たちはroku cody flex youtubeにもいます
google play music podcasts and news book
グーグルプレイ音楽ポッドキャストやニュースブック
or if you're in Southern California tune
またはあなたが南カリフォルニアの 曲にいるならば
in every Sunday morning at 6:30 on kbdb
毎週日曜日の朝6:30にkbdbに
TV channel 33 television for the high
テレビチャンネル33 最高のテレビ
desert
砂漠
[Music]
[音楽]
you
君は